[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the following division problem, the quotient is 2: \n\n12 / 6 = 2.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the top speed that the Red Fox can reach?", "correct_answer": "45 mph", "incorrect_answers": ["25 mph", "35 mph", "55 mph"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did Bruce Willis portray in the popular TV sitcom Friends?", "correct_answer": "The father of Ross girlfriend", "incorrect_answers": ["Monicas first love", "Chandlers old buddy", "The flame of Rachels sister"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These creatures look like flowers as they grow attached to rocks. Their tentacles open like fleshy petals and contract whenever danger is near.", "correct_answer": "Sea Anemones", "incorrect_answers": ["Kelp", "Jellyfish", "Sponges"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Mother Gooses cat in the self-titled newspaper comic strip?", "correct_answer": "Attila", "incorrect_answers": ["Princess", "Angel", "The Duchess"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Across the Hall, Friends Like Us, Insomnia Caf and Six of One are all working titles of one of famous US TV-series.  Name the series.", "correct_answer": "Friends", "incorrect_answers": ["Sex and the City", "ALF", "One Tree Hill"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This skirt-like undergarment was worn for warmth or to give a skirt or dress the desired fashionable shape.", "correct_answer": "Petticoat", "incorrect_answers": ["Camisole", "Panty hose", "Bustle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The traditional Japanese dish, sushi, is always made with raw fish.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This English actor and portrayer of detective Hercule Poirot played Julia Roberts boss in the movie Erin Brockovich.", "correct_answer": "Albert Finney", "incorrect_answers": ["Terence Stamp", "Alan Bates", "Aaron Eckhart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why was the Angel food cake, also known as Angel Cake, called so?", "correct_answer": "Because it is very light", "incorrect_answers": ["Because the creator of the recipe was named Angela", "All of these", "Because it is white"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Big Smoky Valley, that runs between the Toiyabe Range and the Toquima Range, is located in which US state?", "correct_answer": "Nevada", "incorrect_answers": ["Minnesota", "Indiana", "Oregon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these continents represent the natural habit of the cactus?", "correct_answer": "South and North America", "incorrect_answers": ["North America and Africa", "North America, South America and Africa", "South America and Africa"]}]